<rooms>
<room name = "a Dream"> <!-- Room 0 -->
	<description>You float midspace, the room shrouded in white. A blurry figure tips its fedora at you.</description>

	<exit>-1,-1,-1,-1,-1,1</exit>
</room>
<room name = "Your Mom's Basement"> <!-- Room 1 -->
	<description>The only thing you can see is illuminated by the light of the computer. The light shines on a Dorito chip.
Wait... Doritos are triangles... No... It couldn't be...</description>
	<item name = "Doritos">Cool Ranch Doritos. Is there any other way? Frito-Lays knows how to do it, baby. 
But wait... That last chip was a triangle... A thought sparked in your mind... You must tell somebody...
The Illuminati must be at it again.
	</item>
	<item name = "Mountain Dew">Light filters through the bubbles. The shadow cast is a beautiful, fluorescent green.</item>
	<exit>-1,-1,-1,-1,2,-1</exit> <!-- North, not South, not East, not West, not Up, not Down -->
</room>
<room name = "Your Mom's Living Room"> <!-- Room 2 -->
	<description>Your mother sits knitting you a huge sweater. 
She puts down her knitting and says "What is it sweetie? Do you need more Frito-Lay Brand Doritos(R) Cool Ranch(R) Flavored Tortilla Chips(tm)?"
You avoid eye contact. You can't trust her. You can't trust anyone. 
	</description>
	<item name = "Family Photo">You see a picture of you, your mother, and your little sister. Three people form a triangle...</item>
	<exit>4,-1,-1,-1,3,1</exit> <!-- Up(2),Down(0),West(3) -->
</room>
<room name = "Your Sibling's Room"> <!-- Room 3 -->
	<description>
Your sister is on the computer. A triangle rotates on her screen. She doesn't notice you walk in. She is really absorbed in that triangle...
"Frito-Lay Brand Doritos(R) Cool Ranch(R) Flavored Tortilla Chips(tm)," she chants under her breath.
	</description>
	<exit>-1,-1,-1,-1,-1,2</exit>
</room>
<room name = "Outside"> <!-- Room 4 -->
	<description>The sky is bright and hurts to look at. A flaming cancer machine floats high in the sky. You can feel the radiation
clinging and digging under your skin.
You don't know how long you'll be able to last out here.
	</description>
	<item name = "Flower">So pleasant. Smells good.</item>
	<exit>4,4,4,2,-1,-1</exit>
</room>
</rooms>